[
  {
    "question": "Hi1",
    "choice1": "<title> </body>",
    "choice2": "<head> </head>",
    "choice3": "<table> </table>",
    "choice4": "<body> </body>",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi2",
    "choice1": "Google",
    "choice2": "Mozilla",
    "choice3": "WWWC",
    "choice4": "Microsoft",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi3",
    "choice1": "<title> </body>",
    "choice2": "<head> </head>",
    "choice3": "<table> </table>",
    "choice4": "<body> </body>",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi4",
    "choice1": "Google",
    "choice2": "Mozilla",
    "choice3": "WWWC",
    "choice4": "Microsoft",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi5",
    "choice1": "<title> </body>",
    "choice2": "<head> </head>",
    "choice3": "<table> </table>",
    "choice4": "<body> </body>",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi6",
    "choice1": "Google",
    "choice2": "Mozilla",
    "choice3": "WWWC",
    "choice4": "Microsoft",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi7",
    "choice1": "<title> </body>",
    "choice2": "<head> </head>",
    "choice3": "<table> </table>",
    "choice4": "<body> </body>",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi8",
    "choice1": "Google",
    "choice2": "Mozilla",
    "choice3": "WWWC",
    "choice4": "Microsoft",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi9",
    "choice1": "<title> </body>",
    "choice2": "<head> </head>",
    "choice3": "<table> </table>",
    "choice4": "<body> </body>",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi10",
    "choice1": "Google",
    "choice2": "Mozilla",
    "choice3": "WWWC",
    "choice4": "Microsoft",
    "answer": 3
  }
]
